<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language>
    
    <display_name>Single Sign On</display_name>
    <icon>fa-key</icon>
    <description>
        Integrated Single Sign On with major Social Networks.
        Extends the Accounts module to allow the connection of existing accounts with Social Networks.
        Note: Facebook is the only one supported at the moment.
    </description>
    
    <login_with_facebook>Login with Facebook</login_with_facebook>
    
    <facebook>
        <invitation>Do you have a Facebook account?</invitation>
        <connect>Connect with Facebook</connect>
        <user_connected>This user has a Facebook account conected with a local account.</user_connected>
        <already_connected>You have your Facebook account conected with your local account.</already_connected>
        <cannot_connect_other>You cannot have a Facebook account connected to more than one user account on this website.</cannot_connect_other>
        <not_connected>Do you have a Facebook account? You can connect it with your local account!</not_connected>
        <go_to_my_facebook_page>Go to my Facebook page</go_to_my_facebook_page>
        <go_to_user_facebook_page>Go to user's Facebook page</go_to_user_facebook_page>
        <disconnect>Disconnect from Facebook</disconnect>
        <disconnect_prompt><![CDATA[
            Note: your Facebook account will be unlinked from your local
            profile, but no notification will be sent to Facebook.
             
            Your local account won't be deleted. Your current session
            will remain open until you logout.
             
            If you didn't set a password for your account, you will have to
            request a reset from the login form and use your user name or
            alias to login afterwards.
             
            Do you want to proceed?
        ]]></disconnect_prompt>
    </facebook>
    
    <edit_my_profile>Edit my local profile</edit_my_profile>
    
    <messages>
        <session_token_not_found>Session token not found. Please reload the page and try again.</session_token_not_found>
        <facebook>
            <error_on_remote_call>Error on call to Facebook API: </error_on_remote_call>
            <missing_app_id>Sorry, but Facebook App Id isn't set. Please ask an admin to enter it on the Settings.</missing_app_id>
            <missing_app_secret>Sorry, but Facebook App Secret key isn't set. Please ask an admin to enter it on the Settings.</missing_app_secret>
            <missing_account_id>Facebook account id not provided</missing_account_id>
            <missing_account_name>Facebook account name not provided</missing_account_name>
            <missing_account_email>Facebook account email not provided</missing_account_email>
            <missing_access_token>Facebook access token for the account not provided</missing_access_token>
            <account_not_linked>This local account is not linked to any Facebook account</account_not_linked>
            <already_linked>Sorry, but your Facebook account is already linked to another account on this website. You should logout now and login with Facebook to get to the actual linked account.</already_linked>
        </facebook>
        <user_registration_disabled>Sorry, but the accounts registration service is disabled.</user_registration_disabled>
    </messages>
    
    <settings_data>
        <title>Single Sign On</title>
        
        <specs key="facebook_app_id">
            <title><![CDATA[
                <span class="framed_content inlined">Facebook</span>
                App Id
            ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[
                Specify the Facebook App Id for your website.<br>
                <i class="fa fa-info-circle"></i>
                <b>Warning:</b> if you're using any other module for Facebook
                (like the Facebook Comments module),
                you must make sure that you're using the same App Id or the Facebook SDK
                will fail.
            ]]></description>
            <type>number</type>
        </specs>
        
        <specs key="facebook_app_secret">
            <title><![CDATA[
                <span class="framed_content inlined">Facebook</span>
                App Secret
            ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[
                Specify your Facebook App Secret key.<br>
                <i class="fa fa-info-circle"></i>
                <b>Warning:</b> if you're using any other module for Facebook
                that also requires your App Secret,
                you must make sure that you're using the same key or the Facebook SDK
                will fail.
            ]]></description>
            <type>text</type>
        </specs>
        
    </settings_data>
    
</language>
